Mss.B.F865
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence
  - Letters to [John Fries Frazer], Nov. 16, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to Rogers. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Nov. 17, 1859; 8-1/2x5-1/4; Porter, Edward D.
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks for recommendation.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Nov. 29, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Philadelphia, Dec. 7, 1859; 10x8; Smithsonian Institution.
    Washington, L.S.: Joseph Henry. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry,no.16.) Formerly B F865.h. Inquires of a fund for experiments at Franklin Institute. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, Dec. 19, 1859; 7-3/4x5; Alexander, J. H. (John Henry), 1812-1867
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Introduces Prof. Sinding of Denmark. Refers to A.D.Bache.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Dec. 22, 1859; 12-1/2x8; Henry, Mathew Schropp, 1790-1862
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Concerning the Delaware Indians' language. Freeman Guide 1167.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March, 1860; 10x8; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to the University of Pennsylvania. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 5, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Asks help to purchase tools. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, March 13, 1860; 7-3/4x5; Alexander, J. H. (John Henry), 1812-1867
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning certain woods.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, March 22, 1860; 8x5; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 17.) Formerly B F865.h. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 24, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April 4, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning thermometers. Refers to the Franklin institute. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April 10, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning an instrument. Friendly letter. Refers to Agassiz. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, April 13, 1860; 7-1/2x5; Schaeffer, Charles Frederick, 1807-1879
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see-Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) University business.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April 14, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D. Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Thermometers arrived all broken. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April 18, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April 27, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Business of the coast survey. Refers to Agassiz. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, April 28, 1860; 10-3/4x8-1/4; Bartol, B. H.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the construction of steam boilers.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 10, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning his post at the university of Pennsylvania. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 14, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, May 21, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Concerning Humboldt and Agassiz. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 22, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, May 23, 1860; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Hayes, I. I, (Isaac Israel), 1832-1881
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Business.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, June 26, 1860; 8x5; Fraley, F., (Frederick), 1804-1901
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Introduces Mr. Pauly.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, July 4, 1860; 10x7-3/4; University of Pennsylvania. Trustees
    A.L.S.: C.K. Biddle. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Thanks for his services.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 8, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Boston, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Sept. 9, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning Persifor and other young people. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Oct. 3, 1860; 10x7-3/4; Whitehead, William A. (William Adee), 1810-1884
    West Chester, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the Mason and Dixon line.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Nov. 14, 1860; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    New York, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Nov. 28, 1860; 7x4-1/2; Peirce, Benjamin, 1809-1880
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning his and Agassiz's recommendation of a provost for the university of Pennsylvania.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Dec. 10, 1860; 10x7-1/2; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 18.) Formerly B F865.h. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April, 1861; 7-1/4x5; Hassler, Mark
    Philadelphia, L. 1p. Lithograph copy(?) (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Invites him to his farewell concert.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, March 1, 1861; 10x7-3/4; Peck & Bliss
    Philadelphia, L. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Forwards publications.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 16, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 27, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 28, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3P. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, April 4, 1861; 8x5; Guillott
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, April 5, 1861; 7-3/4x5; Alexander, J. H. (John Henry), 1812-1867
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Refers to Henry and A.D.Bache.
  - Letter to [Alexander Dallas] Bache, May 2, 1861; 8x5; Wright, H. G.
    Washington, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning appointments to West Point. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 5, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. News of the war. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 20, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 24, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. News of the war. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 2, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning an appointment to West Point. News of the war. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [Simon Cameron], June 7, 1861; 8x5; Scott, Winfield, 1786-1866
    Washington, L. 2p. Copy. End.: "Commd.Privately to Prof.Frazer..." (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) War news.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 3, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning a West Point appointment. News of the war. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 6, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, July 10, 1861; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Guillott
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning a stroke of lightning. Includes newspaper clipping.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 23, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 30, 1861; 10x7-3/4; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials, 1p. (see Frazer Papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning the appointment of cadets to the military academy. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 31, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning appointment of cadets to the military academy. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 3, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. News of Washington. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 5, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 6, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 8, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning an appointment to West Point for Persifor. News of the war. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Aug. 11, 1861; 8-1/4x5; Kleebury, Charles W.
    Camden, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks to borrow money. Refers to Seward
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 12, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache. ) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to Agassiz. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 22, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 26, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4P. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. News of the war and of Washington. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 29, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4P. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Concerning the war. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Sept. 1, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Sept. 12, 1861; 9-3/4x8; Kleebury, Charles W.
    Washington, A.L.S. 6p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning his plans on education. Refers to Seward and A.D.Bache.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Sept. 18, 1861; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Washington news. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Sept. 24, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Boston, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Concerning Agassiz. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Oct. 15, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    New Canaan, Maine, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letter from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning the sinking of a ship and of Reed and his family. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Oct. 22, 1861; 8x5; Alexander, J. H. (John Henry), 1812-1867
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Introduces Eugene Alexander.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Nov. 13, 1861; 8x5-1/2; Baird, Spencer Fullerton, 1823-1887
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Nov. 25, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Dec. 12, 1861; 8x5; Stillé, Alfred, 1813-1900
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Notifies him of public affairs.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 24, 1861; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Thursday evening [?]. A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Jan. 5, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 18, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 30, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D. Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. News of the war. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Feb. 25, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to Lesley. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 16, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to Jo[h]n F[ries] Frazer, May 16, 1862; 10x7-3/4; McAllister, John A.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S 1p. (see Frazer papers. correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Will keep appointment.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 20, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to J[ohn] Fries] Frazer, July 3, 1862; 9-3/4x8; Poesch, Theodor
    Philadelphia, Washington, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks favor.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 5, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. News of the war. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, July 17, 1862; 7x4-1/2; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
    Nahant, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 16.) Formerly B F865.a. Friendly letter. Wishes to give lectures in Philadelphia. Film 1249
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Aug. 5, 1862; 8x5; Taylor, William J. R. (William James Romeyn), 1823-1891
    A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning bricks in a kiln.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], August 25, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Boston, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. News of the war. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Sept. 8, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Bristol, R.I., A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Sept. 9, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Bristol, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to Fairman Rogers. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Sept. 12, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to Fairman Rogers. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Oct. 31, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John [Fries] Frazer, Philadelphia, Nov. 21, 1862; 10-1/2x8; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 19.). Formerly B F865.h. Agrees to a request. Film 1249
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 8, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Concerning the war. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 12, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Scientific news. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 13, 1862; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. News of the war. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 13, 1862; 8x5; Stillé, Alfred, 1813-1900
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Notice of a meeting.
  - Professor Agassiz's Lectures, [1862?]
    Broadside. Advertises lectures held in Philadelphia. Film 1249. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 17). Formerly B F865.a.
    Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Jan. 6, 1863; 8x5; Marcou, Jules, 1824-1898
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 4p. In French. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning geology. Refers to Agassiz
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 9, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 10, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to LeConte. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 22, 1863; 8x5; Marcou, Jules, 1824-1898
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 1p. In French. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Feb. 3, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Feb. 6, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Business. Refers to Henry. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, March 5, 1863; 10x8; Wilson, Henry, 1812-1875
    L. 2p. Copy. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the national academy of sciences.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 7, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning the university of Pennsylvania and S.Weir Mitchell. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 10, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Scientific business. Refers to Henry. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 12, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Scientific affairs. Refers to VanBuren. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, March 18, 1863; 10x8; Wilson, Henry, 1812-1875
    Washington, L. 1p. Copy. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Arranges for meeting for the national academy of sciences.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April 7, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Organization of the national academy of sciences. Refers to Agassiz and Henry. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April 17, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Business of the national academy of science. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, April 18, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 1, 1863; 8x5; Caswell, Alexis, 1799-1877
    Providence, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the constitution of the national academy of sciences.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 4, 1863; 8x5; Caswell, Alexis, 1799-1877
    Providence, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the constitution of the national academy of sciences.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, May 13, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Circular concerning his lectures, May 14, 1863; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Schaeffer, Charles Frederick, 1807-1879
    Philadelphia, D.S. 4p.and add.: J.F. Frazer. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.)
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 15, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 20, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer, papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to Gideon Welles, May 21, 1863; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Davis, Charles Henry, 1807-1877
    Washington, L. 1p. Copy. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Wishes to discontinue certain government aid to navigation.
  - Letter to A[lexander] D[allas] Bache, May 23, 1863; 9-1/2x7-3/4; Davis, Charles Henry, 1807-1877